YOUSSEF FDIL BADDOUR

Full Stack Developer | C# · Entity FrameWork · React.js · Angular · React Native | Creating Modern, Minimalist

Olot, Spain · fdilyoussef@gmail.com

Summary

Computer Engineering student from Spain with a passion for programming, design, and creativity. Proficient in various programming languages and experienced with UI/UX design tools like Figma and Adobe XD.

Skills

- Proficient in multiple programming languages.
- UI/UX design with Figma and Adobe XD.
- Strong communication and teamwork abilities.

Experience

EIO

Full-Stack Developer,

June 2023 — Present

Jan 2024 - Present

- Developed full-stack applications using C# ASP.NET API and Angular.
- · Built and maintained enterprise software solutions with C# Windows Forms and Entity Framework.
- Collaborated with team members to plan and implement software architectures.
- · Optimized application performance and ensured scalability.
- Participated in code reviews and daily stand-up meetings to improve development workflows.

Skills: C#, Angular, Windows Forms, Entity Framework, SQL Server, Git

Education

IES Bosc de la Coma

SMR Sep 2020 — May 2022

Windows server, Linux, HTML, CSS, Javascript, WordPress

IES Bosc de la coma

DAM Sep 2022 — May 2024

WPF, POO, ASP.NET Web API, MySQL, Docker, MongoDB, Kotlin, Android Studio, Java, Entity FrameWork

Languages

- English
- Spanish Native
- Darija Native (Arabic)